i just wrote a response
on facebook to somebody and i used the
word incompetent in it
just directly referring to our
governments and corporations
and all of the complex meta problems
that are there and i had to google
the definition of a competent because i
didn't want to
be using it wrong and it was the
definition was something along the lines
of they are inadequately equipped
and i'm like yep inadequate is good then
the corporations and governments are in
no way able to solve our
current problems we can with ten
thousand people and a hundred thousand
dollars
the comment was actually in response to
a request i put out there to find some
audacious
problems that a solution raising can't
tackle can't improve
with ten thousand people and a hundred
thousand dollars and someone put up
climate change
and we haven't actually tackled that yet
but then they offered a response
um of a solution and
it's like actually like the point
of a solution isn't to actually solve it
it's to drastically improve it
either for the world or for those 10 000
members but for the world it has to be
voluntary
ten thousand people can get together and
create a new carbon tax that we're gonna
demand everybody use
it's just not as it's not effective as
creating something that is
voluntary and what you want to put into
the world
but this concept of incompetence
that who we currently have in power
who are all in positions of prestige are
the people who fake
competence are the people who either
themselves think they are qualified
and can present that to the world and
our society is set up very much
for the overestimators and the risk
takers basically because they don't see
the risk
so they're gonna go to take it like just
think positively
and we're seeing the outfit the um
outcomes of that
that many of the businesses are failing
and the ones that aren't failing are
being bailed out by the government
because not to disparage business owners
but those that were successful
had to have a high risk tolerance so
they you
just can't sit on three months worth of
savings
knowing that a catastrophe is coming in
the marketplace you have to spend it
even if you would have preferred to save
it
and really the personalities themselves
are
are uh again our society set up
to put people in positions of power that
appear competent
but they are not competent in fact the
very people who we think of as
incompetent
people with disabilities people who
struggle people who
have had the world not work for them are
actually the people who have a low risk
tolerance
the underestimators are actually better
at this stuff
but i get that the people who are at the
top are never going to see that but i
don't need them to
i need the people who are hearing this
message who think themselves as
incompetent
to get that you are not you are just an
underestimator
you can come and raise solutions to all
of the issues that
impact your life and the world you are
enough exactly as you are
and together we can solve or we can
drastically improve
every area with ten thousand people and
a hundred thousand dollars
not ten thousand billionaires not ten
thousand people with
fifteen phds
is there even enough time in your
lifetime adhds
that you exactly as you are with your
thoughts and your ideas and your
personality
can come and create solutions that work
if it calls you can host solution
raisings it's franchisable
literally just host one with your
friends and family or
come to ours at 9am pacific standard
time join the facebook group to get the
link
or email me at collaborativedemocracy
gmail.com
we can create the solutions to
every area because we can drastically
improve them and keep improving them
we improve them for the ten thousand we
do improve them for the world
we're just not doing it on their behalf
to sell it to them
please trust us we're doing it with them
and for them because with
them the them is us we're the us we're
the them
it's the same so i just wanted to share
that this morning
incompetence and overs underestimation
which i'll probably do its own video on
because it's also been something that
has been
coming up since the beginning pandemic
for me and really just life in general
and the constructions are starting all
right good
bye see you later